<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SAAR</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--About Us Page-->
    <string name="about_us_fragment">About Us fragment</string>
    <string name="home_fragment">Home fragment</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="background">Background</string>
    <string name="objectives">Objectives</string>
    <string name="missions">Missions</string>
    <string name="initiatives">Initiatives</string>

    <string name="about_us_background_details">Indian Institute of Technology Patna is an Institution of National Importance
        and a new addition to the hallowed IIT System that has proven its worth in last 50+ years. The alumni of IIT are
        internationally known for their caliber and contribution. Since its inception in 2008, IIT Patna- like its young as
        well as established peers- has pursued excellence with steadfast determination. \n\n IITP has 6 Engineering Disciplines:
        Civil and Environmental Engineering, Chemical and Biochemical Engineering, Computer Science and Engineering,
        Electrical Engineering, Mechanical Engineering and Material Science and Engineering; 2 Science Disciplines:
        Physics and Chemistry; Humanities and Social Sciences; Mathematics. Its faculty members are experts in their
        respective fields. The thriving PhD, M.Tech and B.Tech programs of IITP see the students and faculty publish
        prolifically, win competitions, come up with innovations and build societal awareness.</string>

    <string name="about_us_objectives_details">Established in 2018, Students Association for Alumni Relations (SAAR),
        has been created to maintain a life-long connection between the Institute and its alumni (more than 1500 at present).
        The committee works in coordination with the institute to create a platform that helps in connecting the former students
        with their alma mater \n\n Filled with extremely dedicated volunteers, SAAR works to connect alumni, support students and
        build an unforgettable Institute experience through a diversity of events, programming and services. With the purpose of
        creating a strong network of alumni, guiding and mentoring juniors, developing the institute, SAAR works towards
        creating strong alumni relations.</string>

    <string name="about_us_missions_details">A bond binds us to the place that guides us towards a fun-filled and fulfilling future.......
        and that place is our college. No matter where we go, no matter how old our bones grow, bonds always remain strong. We plan
        on bringing old ‘Partners in Crime’ back together and for that the primary mission of SAAR (Students’ Association for Alumni Relations)
        is to create a connection with all the Alumni of IIT Patna and to strengthen that relation. We also plan on getting in touch with our
        Alumni residing in other countries.\n\n SAAR aims at spending a defined portion of its manpower, intelligence and resources for the
        betterment of society through: \n\n
        Educational and other assistance to students belonging to socially/economically weaker sections. \n\n
        Promoting, encouraging and supporting the social and cultural heritage and traditions of our society. \n\n
        Proactive actions for well-being of the society as per the needs. \n\n
        Incorporating sustainability in education plans, strategies and processes.</string>

    <string name="about_us_initiatives_details">SAAR plans on creating a discussion forum, where students can interact with the Alumni to get their
        doubts answered.Along with this, SAAR plans on conducting Alumni Chapter in various cities across the country to enhance the relations.\n\n
        To further strengthen the relations between the Alumni and the institute, SAAR also conducts felicitation programs and Alumni talks. \n\n
        SAAR is in process (via regular talks and discussions) to bring reputed industries so as to encourage them to set up research centers and
        collaborative program through them. The proposed center is expected to be set up with a funding from these industries inside IITP campus
        and IITP will deliver the knowledge base to give a meaningful solution to their day to day industrial challenges, problems etc.\n\n
        Through National Service Scheme (NSS) activities SAAR is already actively working for the empowered of impoverished sections of humanity and
        for the nearby villages around IITP campus apart from donation of books, copies and clothes to these society people IITP students are
        also teaching them on a regular basis.</string>
</resources>
